Finding Aid for Donald W. Riegle, Jr. papers
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Senatorial Papers, 1977-1994
  - Constituent Mail, 1977-1993
    - 4268013801 -- 4285013083 (Reel 370)
    - 2850013084 -- 4303013012 (Reel 371)
    - 4303013012 -- 4321051021 (Reel 372)
    - 4321051022 -- 4341013135 (Reel 373)
    - 4342051001 -- 4355013306 (Reel 374)
    - 5003013001 -- 5008013096 (Reel 375)
    - 5009051001 -- 5021 (Reel 376)
    - 5021-- 5030 (Reel 377)
    - 5030-- 5036 (Reel 378)
    - 5036-- 5044 (Reel 379)
    - 5044-- 5046 (Reel 380)
    - 5046-- 5058 (Reel 381)
    - 5058-- 5065 (Reel 382)
    - 5066-5072 (Reel 383)
    - 5072-- 5073 (Reel 384)
    - 5073-- 5079 (Reel 385)
    - 5079-- End (Reel 386)
    - 5197013001 -- to be continued (Reel 387)
    - 5197013001 -- 5080073001 (Reel 388)
    - 5080073001 -- 5086073001 (Reel 389)
    - 5086073001 -- 508801340 (Reel 390)
    - 508801340 -- 5094051039 (Reel 391)
    - 5094051040 -- 5095013510 (Reel 392)
    - 5095013510 -- 5106051001 (Reel 393)
    - 5106051002 -- 5106013457 (Reel 394)
    - 5106013457 -- 1350-R-04-08-85 (Reel 395)
    - 5109051001 -- 5114073685 (Reel 396)
    - 5114073686 -- 5120051064 (Reel 397)
    - 5120051064 -- 5123051091 (Reel 398)
    - 5123051091 -- 5129073841 (Reel 399)
    - 5129073830 -- 5135051064 (Reel 400)
    - 5135013001 -- 5140053132 (Reel 401)
    - 5140053133 -- 5143013001 (Reel 402)
    - 5143013001 -- 5151051019 (Reel 403)
    - 5155053001 -- 5156073841 (Reel 404)
    - 5156073841-5157051131 (Reel 405)
    - 5157051132 -- 5161013689 (Reel 406)
    - 5161013690 -- 5169053109 (Reel 407)
    - 5169053110 -- 5176051006 (Reel 408)
    - 5176051007 -- 5184013809 (Reel 409)
    - 5184013810 -- 5198051090 (Reel 410)
    - 5199051001 -- 5205051075 (Reel 411)
    - 5205051074 -- 5212051122 (Reel 412)
    - 5213051001 -- 5217014131 (Reel 413)
    - 5217014112 -- 5220013409 (Reel 414)
    - 5220-- 5232 (Reel 415)
    - 5232-- 5232 (Reel 416)
    - 5232-- 5253 (Reel 417)
    - 5254013001 -- 5254014451 (Reel 418)
    - 5254014452 -- 5266051086 (Reel 419)
    - 5266-- 5267 (Reel 420)
    - 5267-- 5268 (Box 161, Reel 421)
    - 1 5270013908, October 1985 (Reel 422)
    - 5270013409 -- 5276013352 (Reel 423)
    - 5276013353 -- 5289013449 (Reel 424)
    - 5282013395 -- 5289013307 (Reel 425)
    - 5291051001-Harrigan (Reel 426)
    - 5204013861 -- 5309051001 (Reel 427)
    - 5298013001 -- 5300013671 (Reel 428)
    - 5303013011 -- 5312013939 (Reel 429)
    - 5312013001 -- 379544 (Reel 430)
    - 5319013825 -- 5319014052 (Reel 431)
    - 5322051001 -- 5329051044 (Reel 432)
    - 5329051045 -- 5336014073 (Reel 433)
    - 5336-- 5346 (Reel 434)
    - 5346-- Letter from Collin, Pauline Hoskin (Reel 435)
    - Letter John-Dorothy Teasdale -- 1548A12098 (Reel 436)
    - Nancy Sanke -- 6014051027 (Reel 437)
    - 6014051027 -- 6028051046 (Reel 438)
    - 6028051046 -- 6036051144 (Reel 439)
    - 6037051001 -- 6049905007 (Reel 440)
    - 60499051010 -- 6051013393 (Reel 441)
    - 605101393 -- 6057013040 (Reel 442)
    - 6057013041 -- 6062051105 (Reel 443)
    - 6062051106 -- 6064013939 (Reel 444)
    - 6065013001 -- 6071051011 (Reel 445)
    - 6071051012 -- 6077013198 (Reel 446)
    - 6085013001 -- 6085054011 (Reel 447)
    - 6085054162 -- 6090011051 (Reel 448)
    - 6090011051 -- 6099011019 (Reel 449)
    - 6099011019 -- 6085013287 (Reel 450)
    - 6085013418 -- 6119013001 (Reel 451)
    - 6119013201 -- 6121011038 (Reel 452)
    - 6121011046 -- 6125054509 (Reel 453)
    - 6125054509 -- 6128051086 (Reel 454)
    - 6128051097 -- 6129051024 (Reel 455)
    - 6133051001 -- to be continued (Reel 456)
    - 6133051001 -- 6136014234 (Reel 457)
    - 3238-- Item #457 (Reel 458)
    - 457052086 -- 6147051023 (Reel 459)
    - 6147-- 6149 (Reel 460)
    - 6149051009 -- 6155051001 (Reel 461)
    - 6135051001 -- 6161051020 (Reel 462)
    - 6161051033 -- 6168051009 (Reel 463)
    - CMS letters -- CMS letters (Reel 464)
    - CMS letters -- CMS letters (Reel 465)
    - CMS letters -- CMS letters (Reel 466)
    - CMS letters -- CMS letters (Reel 467)
    - CMS letters -- CMS letters (Reel 468)
    - CMS letters -- CMS letters (Reel 469)
    - CMS letters -- CMS letters (Reel 470)
    - CMS letters -- CMS letters (Reel 471)
    - CMS letters -- CMS letters (Reel 472)
    - CMS letters A -- CMS letters M (Reel 473)
    - CMS letters -- CMS letters (Reel 474)
    - 6205051041 -- 6209051086 (Reel 475)
    - 6209051097 -- 6211013954 (Reel 476)
    - 6211013955 -- 6217013230 (Reel 477)
    - 6217013231 -- 6219013083 (Reel 478)
    - 6219013084 -- 6224051056 (Reel 479)
    - 6224051057 -- 6238051213 (Reel 480)
    - 6238053001 -- 6247051086 (Reel 481)
    - 6248013001 -- 6251053262 (Reel 482)
    - 6251053262 -- 6253013652 (Reel 483)
    - 6253013652 -- 6258051076 (Reel 484)
    - 6259051001 -- 6260051001 (Reel 485)
    - 6260051002 -- 6265051044 (Reel 486)
    - 6265051045 -- 6275013526 (Reel 487)
    - 6275013527 -- 6289051037 (Reel 488)
    - 6289051038 -- 6314051051 (Reel 489)
    - 6314013001 -- 6316051127 (Reel 490)
    - 6316051128 -- 6232014104 (Reel 491)
    - 6232014105 -- 6329051096 (Reel 492)
    - 6335051001 -- 6353051078 (Reel 493)
    - 6353051079 -- Blackwell (Reel 494)
    - Helen Saunders -- 7033051087 (Reel 495)
    - 7033051087 -- 7051013224 (Reel 496)
    - 7051013234 -- 7056013432 (Reel 497)
    - 7056013436 -- 7069051059 (Reel 498)
    - 7069051060 -- 7084051049 (Reel 499)
    - 7084013001 -- 7085051106 (Reel 500)
    - 7086051001 -- 7091013001 (Reel 501)
    - 7091013001 -- 7097051186 (Reel 502)
    - 7098051001 -- 7106051050 (Reel 503)
    - 7106051051 -- 7117013063 (Reel 504)
    - 7117013064 -- 7120051006 (Box 162, Reel 505)
    - 7120051006 -- 7128013359 (Reel 506)
    - 7128013359 -- 7139213409 (Reel 507)
    - 7139213410 -- 7147051039 (Reel 508)
    - 7147051040 -- 7154013625 (Reel 509)
    - 7154013625 (Reel 510)
    - 8004051001 -- 8015013620 (Reel 511a)
    - 8015013630-8027051045 (Reel 512)
    - 8027051045 -- 8048051032 (Reel 513)
    - 8053051001 -- 8071013001 (Reel 514)
    - 8071015029 -- 8071013001 (Reel 515)
    - 8071013001 -- 8071013793 (Reel 516)
    - 8074013001 -- 8078011069 (Reel 517)
    - 8078011069 -- 8091051001 (Reel 518)
    - 8091051001 -- 8102051100 (Reel 519)
    - 8102051106 -- 8104051078 (Reel 520)
    - 8104051079 -- 8109051077 (Reel 521)
    - 8109051078 -- 8112014112 (Reel 522)
    - 8113051001 -- 8117033056 (Reel 523)
    - 8117033158 -- 8124033466 (Reel 524)
    - 8124033466 -- 8130051058 (Reel 525)
    - 8130051059 -- 8133034194 (Reel 526)
    - 8133034195 -- 8133053590 (Reel 527)
    - 8133053591 -- 8137033232 (Reel 528)
    - 8137033233 -- 8189053750 (Reel 529)
    - 8137033233 -- 8141051134 (Reel 530)
    - 8148051001 -- 8152051171 (Reel 531)
    - 8153051001 -- 8162033404 (Reel 532)
    - 8162033400 -- 8162054057 (Reel 533)
    - 8162054058 -- 8169 (Reel 534)
    - 8169-- 8176 (Reel 535)
    - 8176-- 8018 (Reel 536)
    - 8180-- 8182 (Reel 537)
    - 8182-- 8188 (Reel 538)
    - 8188-- 8193 (Reel 539)
    - 8193-- 8196051036 (Reel 540)
    - 8196051037 -- 8201051079 (Reel 541)
    - 8202033001 -- 8208051059 (Reel 542)
    - 8208051060 -- 8211033414 (Reel 543)
    - 8211033413 -- 8221033149 (Reel 544)
    - 8222031001 -- 8229033106 (Reel 545)
    - 8230051010 -- 8238033252 (Reel 546)
    - 8238033197 -- 8251051046 (Reel 547)
    - 8251051046 -- 8257033136 (Reel 548)
    - 8257033137 -- 8264051057 (Reel 549)
    - 8264051057 -- 8271051148 (Reel 550)
    - 8271051148 -- 8274051054 (Reel 551)
    - 8274051054 -- 8285033098 (Reel 552)
    - 8285033173 -- 8293051001 (Reel 553)
    - 8293051001 -- 8299033180 (Reel 554)
    - 8300031001 -- 8312013615 (Reel 555)
    - 8315033001 -- 8323031005 (Reel 556)
    - 8323031005 -- 8340033068 (Reel 557)
    - 8341033026 -- 9017031012 (Reel 558)
    - 9017051001 -- 9027051008 (Reel 559)
    - 9031031001 -- 9045033101 (Reel 560)
    - 9047031001 -- 9059031006 (Reel 561)
    - 9061033001 -- 9072051001 (Reel 562)
    - 9073033001 -- 9081031001 (Reel 563)
    - 9081031001 -- 9097033310 (Reel 564)
    - 9097033269 -- 9097033268 (Reel 565)
    - 9087051001 -- 9102033034 (Reel 566)
    - 9102033342 -- 9108051098 (Reel 567)
    - 9109051001 -- 9114033100 (Reel 568)
    - 9114033101 -- 9118051001 (Reel 569)
    - 9118051001 -- 9123051056 (Reel 570)
    - 9123051056 -- 9131033341 (Reel 571)
    - 9131033001 -- 9138633019 (Reel 572)
    - 9139033001 -- 9150053271 (Reel 573)
    - 9150053281 -- 9150054651 (Reel 574)
    - 9150054652 -- 915103153 (Reel 575)
    - 915103154 -- 9152033424 (Reel 576)
    - 9122011006 -- 9186011020 (Reel 577)
    - 9186011021 -- 9223013001 (Reel 578)
    - 9223013001 -- 9215051001 (Reel 579)
    - 9215051001 -- 9240041001 (Reel 580)
    - 9240041002 -- 9242054033 (Reel 581)
    - 9242054054 -- 9244051086 (Reel 582)
    - 9248051001 -- 9257051001 (Reel 583)
    - Roll 584 level 1--9257051002 -- Clark Phillips
    - Clark Phillips -- 9257037006 (Reel 585)
    - 7215051001 -- 7222051127 (Reel 586)
    - 7225051001 -- 7259051001 (Reel 587)
    - 7265051001 -- 7272051001 (Reel 588)
    - 7281051016 -- 7289012397 (Box 163, Reel 589)
    - 7286051001 -- 7309051122 (Reel 590)
    - 7309051182 -- 7327051143 (Reel 591)
    - 7321013689 -- 7154014254 (Reel 592)
    - 7154014254 -- 7357014236 (Reel 593)
    - 7357014240 -- 7357015588 (Reel 594)
    - 7348051001 -- 7345017576 (Reel 595)
    - 7345017577 -- 7337013605 (Reel 596)
    - 7332013606 -- 9270033204 (Reel 597)
    - 9270033019 -- 93190 (Reel 598)
    - February 3, 1983-August 15, 1986 (Reel 599)
    - August 7, 1986-April 23, 1986 (Reel 600)
    - January 14, 1986-December 3, 1973 (Reel 601)
    - 1974-1982 (Reel 602)
    - St. Paul's Church -- Robert Lawson (Reel 603)
    - Gordon Lindquist -- SSG Anne Fisher (Reel 604)
    - Helen Fuller -- Stuart Parsell (Reel 605)
    - Bob Popieliaz -- Corothy Zentarski (Reel 606)
    - (Labor) Law Reform -- Banking (Reel 607)
    - (Government) General -- C.F.C. Policy (Reel 608)
    - Chris Ayotte Director M. McAvoy, 1981 (Reel 609)
    - Margaret Aoy -- Dave Zylstra (Reel 610)
    - 9349033121 -- 9355033919 (Reel 611)
    - 9355033920 -- 0005033095 (Reel 612)
    - 0005033096 -- 0009033563 (Reel 613)
    - 0009033564 -- 0019054870 (Reel 614)
    - 0019054851 -- 0023053292 (Reel 615)
    - 0023053293 -- 0030031001 (Reel 616)
    - 0030031002 -- 0037031008 (Reel 617)
    - 0037031009 -- 0040031119 (Reel 618)
    - 0016031028 -- 0039031074 (Reel 619)
    - 0075053213 -- 0085031012 (Reel 620)
    - 0085031012 -- 0099053170 (Reel 621)
    - 0099053171 -- 0107031003 (Reel 622)
    - 0107031004 -- 0113053154 (Reel 623)
    - 0113053154 -- 0114053507 (Reel 624)
    - 0114053507 -- 0129053335 (Reel 625)
    - 0131043260 -- 0131043260 (Reel 626)
    - 0132043001 -- 0143031001 (Reel 627)
    - 0143031001 -- 0145053617 (Reel 628)
    - 0145053658 -- 0155053001 (Reel 629)
    - 0155053035 -- 0162031043 (Reel 630)
    - 0102031043 -- 0163053791 (Reel 631)
    - 0163053792 -- 0170051061 (Reel 632)
    - 0170051061 -- 9251011022 (Reel 633)
    - 9251011023 -- 9303033268 (Reel 634)
    - 9303033268 -- 9313011004 (Reel 635)
    - 9313011005 -- 9156033362 (Reel 636)
    - 9156031010 -- 9163051108 (Reel 637)
    - 9163051109 -- 9164033052 (Reel 638)
    - 9164033053 -- 9170033179 (Reel 639)
    - 9171033898 -- 9180054052 (Reel 640)
    - 9258051001 -- 9268051042 (Reel 641)
    - 9268051043 -- 9278033682 (Reel 642)
    - 9279051001 -- 9290053189 (Reel 643)
    - 9284051001 -- 9297051089 (Reel 644)
    - 9297051089 -- 9300034157 (Reel 645)
    - 9300034157 -- 9300036146 (Reel 646)
    - 9300035150 -- 9304033790 (Reel 647)
    - 9304033790 -- 9348051044 (Reel 648)
    - 9348051044 -- 9348051045 (Reel 649)
    - 9346051018 -- 9318051113 (Reel 650)
    - 9318051116 -- 9348033073 (Reel 651)
    - 0010011606 -- 0067011016 (Reel 652)
    - 0072011002 -- 0110011024 (Reel 653)
    - 0110011024 -- 0178051008 (Reel 654)
    - 0178051009 -- 0187031076 (Reel 655)
    - 0187033001 -- 0197033016 (Reel 656)
    - 0197033232 -- 0204053315 (Reel 657)
    - 0074053558 -- 0205033132 (Reel 658)
    - 0205033132 -- 0208051003 (Reel 659)
    - 0208031004 -- 0213031100 (Reel 660)
    - 0213031101 -- 0215053017 (Reel 661)
    - 0215053228 -- 0219051149 (Reel 662)
    - 0201041001-0227051083 (Reel 663)
    - 0228033017 -- 0234033216 (Reel 664)
    - 0234033217 -- 9202033033 (Reel 665)
    - 9205051001 -- 0240051001 (Reel 666)
    - 0240051001 -- 0242033195 (Reel 667)
    - 0243033001 -- 0254053371 (Reel 668)
    - 0254053372 -- 0254034283 (Reel 669)
    - 0254034283 -- 0261053109 (Reel 670)
    - 0261053271 -- 0264031017 (Reel 671)
    - 0267041001 -- 0269051034 (Reel 672)
    - 0271033055 -- 0275033092 (Box 164, Reel 673)
    - 0275033173 -- 0278033055 (Reel 674)
    - 0278053001 -- 0285053250 (Reel 675)
    - 0285053251 -- 0291033649 (Reel 676)
    - 0292031001 -- 0299031012 (Reel 677)
    - 0299031013 -- 0305051004 (Reel 678)
    - 0305051005 -- 0312031005 (Reel 679)
    - 0312031006 -- 0316031051 (Reel 680)
    - 0316041001 -- 0318041001 (Reel 681)
    - 0318041002 -- 0333051001 (Reel 682)
    - 0333051001 -- 0337053539 (Reel 683)
    - 0330031001 -- 0338033105 (Reel 684)
    - 0338033142 -- 0340031029 (Reel 685)
    - 0340043454 -- 0345053689 (Reel 686)
    - 0340033689 -- 0348033047 (Reel 687)
    - 0351033059 -- 0109103103 (Reel 688)
    - 1091031001 -- 1113033066 (Reel 689)
    - 1113033067 -- 1135033134 (Reel 690)
    - 1135033135 -- 1056033220 (Reel 691)
    - 1056033221 -- 1081033160 (Reel 692)
    - 1084033001 -- 1091051162 (Reel 693)
    - 1091053001 -- 1098053884 (Reel 694)
    - 1100053001 -- 1107053443 (Reel 695)
    - 0351051001 -- 0347041007 (Reel 696)
    - 0347041007 -- 1004043893 (Reel 697)
    - 1004043001 -- 1004044143 (Reel 698)
    - 1004044143 -- 1011051037 (Reel 699)
    - 1011051039 -- 1024034113 (Reel 700)
    - 1024034113 -- 1024104242 (Reel 701)
    - 1024104242 -- 1024055112 (Reel 702)
    - 1024055112 -- 1024055288 (Reel 703)
    - 1024055288 -- 1036033379 (Reel 704)
    - 1036031001 -- 1039053557 (Reel 705)
    - 1039053557 -- 1056053299 (Reel 706)
    - 1056053200 -- 1084053156 (Reel 707)
    - 1092041001 -- 1140053324 (Reel 708)
    - 1135053001 -- 1142033039 (Reel 709)
    - 1142033040 -- 1155051035 (Reel 710)
    - 1155051036 -- 1171033155 (Reel 711)
    - 1172033001 -- 1168031001 (Reel 712)
    - 1168031002 -- 1206031001 (Reel 713)
    - 1206031002 -- 1163053271 (Reel 714)
    - 1163053272 -- 1177053094 (Reel 715)
    - 1177053095 -- 1196053319 (Reel 716)
    - 1196053320 -- 1204053001 (Reel 717)
    - 1205051001 -- 1219031045 (Reel 718)
    - 1218051001 -- 1226033112 (Reel 719)
    - 1226033113 -- 1234051032 (Reel 720)
    - 1234051033 -- 1248033061 (Reel 721)
    - 1248033062 -- 1247053425 (Reel 722)
    - 1248033001 -- 1253053726 (Reel 723)
    - 1253053727 -- 1260053163 (Reel 724)
    - 1260051001 -- 1267053001 (Reel 725)
    - 1267053046 -- 1270033122 (Reel 726)
    - 1270031001 -- 1274033101 (Reel 727)
    - 1274033102 -- 1281031001 (Reel 728)
    - 1282053001 -- 1288053014 (Reel 729)
    - 1288053025 -- 1289053451 (Reel 730)
    - 1290033001 -- 1297053825 (Reel 731)
    - 1297053835 -- 1303053411 (Reel 732)
    - 1301031001 -- 1308031023 (Reel 733)
    - 1308031025 -- 1316033001 (Reel 734)
    - 1316033113 -- 1318053001 (Reel 735)
    - 1318053391 -- 1324031001 (Reel 736)
    - 1324041001 -- 1336053095 (Reel 737)
    - 1336053182 -- 0267011004 (Reel 738)
    - 0267011005 -- 0306011031 (Reel 739)
    - 0309011001 -- 1073011041 (Reel 740)
    - 1073011062 -- 1142011013 (Reel 741)
    - 1142011015 -- 1247011023 (Reel 742)
    - 1248011001 -- 1255011062 (Reel 743)
    - 3049033001 -- 3053054041 (Reel 744)
    - 3053054061 -- 2057031116 (Reel 745)
    - 2058033054 -- 3060033689 (Reel 746)
    - 3060034055 -- 3060035633 (Reel 747)
    - 3060035634 -- 3061054598 (Reel 748)
    - 3062033001 -- 3068033333 (Reel 749)
    - 2337031002 -- 1283011028 (Reel 750)
    - 1287011001 -- 2007031002 (Reel 751)
    - 2007031003 -- 2022031128 (Reel 752)
    - 2022031129 -- 2027041001 (Reel 753)
    - 2027041002-2031043099 (Reel 754)